<?xml version="1.0"?>
<article id="20130108055408"><title>A poster puppy for animal rescue</title><bod>PARK RAPIDS, Minn. &#x2013; Six weeks ago, a starving and feces-matted Maltese crossbred was rescued from a cage in a home here where she was left to die.&#xD;
&#xD;
This week, Angel had her stitches out from cancer surgery and seemed bright-eyed. The tail will get bushier with time.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#x201C;She&#x2019;s doing great,&#x201D; said her adopted mom, Rachelle Kern, who works at Headwaters Animal Shelter in Park Rapids and took the little dog in.&#xD;
&#xD;
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
Angel comes to work with Rachelle every day and has become the poster child for the shelter&#x2019;s Herculean efforts to save her.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#x201C;She&#x2019;s even gained a pound!&#x201D; Kern said.&#xD;
&#xD;
Mammarian tumors believed to be malignant were removed from her last week at Ark Animal Hospital, which provides care at a reduced rate to the shelter.&#xD;
&#xD;
<![CDATA[<br/>]]>
<![CDATA[<br/>]]>  
Her prognosis is fair, Kern said. If the tumors metastasize, depending on Angel&#x2019;s health, they will be removed again in the future.&#xD;
&#xD;
Charges are pending against Angel&#x2019;s former owners.&#xD;
&#xD;
Meanwhile Angel&#x2019;s wardrobe is growing thanks to her fans and Kern&#x2019;s co-workers.&#xD;
&#xD;
Thursday she was sporting a pink collar, a pink wool coat with rhinestone buttons and pink nail polish.&#xD;
&#xD;
<![CDATA[<br/>]]>
<![CDATA[<br/>]]>  
She had been so neglected, it took days to make her presentable. She jumps off her bed at Headwaters to greet visitors, but she keeps a close eye on Kern, her savior.&#xD;
&#xD;
She&#x2019;s adjusted well to Kern&#x2019;s house full of dogs, especially the Newfoundland, and office life after abuse, Kern said.&#xD;
&#xD;
She knows she&#x2019;s special. She pushes her tiny nose into your face to nuzzle, Kern said.&#xD;
&#xD;
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
&#x201C;We&#x2019;re crossing our fingers and hoping,&#x201D; Kern said. &#x201C;She&#x2019;s lively and acting like a normal dog would act. There&#x2019;s always a trust issue after something like that.&#x201D;&#xD;
&#xD;
And even if she&#x2019;s on borrowed time, she&#x2019;s living life to the fullest.</bod><pub>Sarah Smith</pub><date>January 04, 2013</date><breed>Maltese</breed></article>
