<?xml version="1.0"?>
<article id="20130108060247"><title>Volunteers Save Thousands of Abused Animals</title><bod>JONESBORO, Ga. -- Abused and abandoned animals continue to crowd county animal shelters and for most of them it's a one-way street.&#xD;
&#xD;
In Clayton County, more than 100 dogs a week are brought in.&#xD;
&#xD;
Few have left.&#xD;
&#xD;
But one volunteer group is working around the clock to save the animals, get them out, and find them new homes.&#xD;
&#xD;
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
Sunny is one of them.&#xD;
&#xD;
She is a 6-month old Lab brought into the Clayton County Animal Shelter, with rescuers saying the abuse she suffered was the worst they have ever seen--a collar embedded in her neck-- with injuries too graphic to show you.&#xD;
&#xD;
She is now with a Vet and is reported in guarded condition after 2 hours of surgery.&#xD;
&#xD;
But tragically, Sunny is not alone--&#xD;
&#xD;
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
"We see a lot of animals that have burns down their back. We see animals that have been shot with guns and we see a lot of embedded collars," said Maria Dorough, founder of Partners for Pets.&#xD;
&#xD;
It prompted Ms. Dorough and a small group of volunteers to start Partners for Pets a year ago to rescue as many animals as possible from the Clayton County Animal Shelter.&#xD;
&#xD;
"Prior to us coming in all the dogs here were pretty much, when they came in the front door they never left," Dorough said.&#xD;
&#xD;
But in one year alone, with Clayton County bringing in more than 6,000 animals, Partners for Pets has been able to rescue 2,500 of them.&#xD;
&#xD;
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
They include many needing immediate care.&#xD;
&#xD;
Partners for Pets rush them to Vets for thorough exams and treatment. From there, they join thousands of other rescued animals that are sent as far away as Alaska to new homes.&#xD;
&#xD;
But no matter what is being done--the abuse continues.&#xD;
&#xD;
"We've got to change the mind set on these dogs. They are not a piece of paper and they are not just property you can just dispose of, these are living breathing animals that have no voice of their own and we are trying to be a voice for these animals," Dorough added.&#xD;
&#xD;
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
Clayton County Police say they are investigating what led to Sunny's injuries. So far no charges have been filed against the dog's owner.&#xD;
&#xD;
If you know of an animal that has been abused, you can move quickly to help in its rescue.&#xD;
&#xD;
The 11Alive Help Desk has prepared a special resource page identifying groups and agencies that will work to save the animals life. &#xD;
&#xD;
The resource page also outlines the proper collars you should be putting on your pets.</bod><pub>Bill Liss</pub><date>January 07, 2013</date><breed>Lab</breed></article>
