<?xml version="1.0"?>
<article id="20130108061121"><title>O.C. shelter seeks help for 3 dogs</title><bod>Orange County Animal Care has put out a call for help for three dogs in its care.&#xD;
The shelter, in Orange, recently has taken in three dogs with broken legs.&#xD;
The dogs &#x2013; Blizzard, Dickens and Comet &#x2013; all have the same injury to their legs, shelter spokeswoman Tammy Osborn said.&#xD;
Comet, who arrived at the shelter first, is a 9-month-old male, probably a terrier mix. His leg has been fixed but the shelter still owes $850 on the bill.
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
 Shelter personnel hope to raise $1,000 each to pay for surgery for 2-year-old Pomeranian mix Dickens and 8-month-old poodle-schnauzer mix Schnoodle to have the same surgery.&#xD;
All three of the little dogs would make great companions, Osborn said. "Help us help these three broken little dogs," she added.&#xD;
Donations of any amount can be made to Noble Friends Foundation via the group's website.&#xD;
If you like cute little dogs and you'd like to help save some unwanted pooches, Bella Pomeranian has a deal for you.&#xD;
The dog has her own Facebook page, , and she also has her own 2013 calendar. 

<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
For $15 you get a year of glossy photos of Bella (who just might give Boo, that famous Facebook Pom, a run for his cuteness money) with all of the proceeds going to Southern California Pomeranian Rescue. More info about the group is available online.&#xD;
Online ordering info is on the Facebook site. To order by snail mail, send a check and your shipping address to Southern California Pomeranian Rescue, 14252 Culver Drive, Suite A-281, Irvine CA 92604.&#xD;
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
Californians who placed orders for the pet lover's license plate can rest assured: They're one step closer to sporting the Pierce Brosnan-designed plates on their cars.&#xD;
As of Wednesday, the 7,500 preorders needed to ensure production of the plates had been received. This means that sometime in 2013, plates should begin arriving at DMV offices, where recipients will exchange their old license plates for the new ones.&#xD;
Preorders will be filled before orders to the general public, according to the official website for the plate,www.petloversplate.com.&#xD;
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 
<![CDATA[<br/>]]> 

Preorders are still being accepted for a limited time, according to the site. Standard plates are $50; personalized plates are $98. Portions of the fees will be distributed to cities and counties to use in free spay and neuter clinics. The goal is to lower the number of unwanted animals born in the state and subsequently killed in shelters.&#xD;
</bod><pub>Maryanne Dell</pub><date>December 25, 2012</date><breed>Terrier mix, Pomeranian mix Dickens, and poodle-schnauzer mix Schnoodle</breed></article>
